Hello, hello everyone. The plan we are
reviewing today is the ICICI
Prudential Guaranteed Pension Plan. It is one of the
best in the market and is available with teachers and staff.
In India, very few people
plan for their pension, and if some do,
they use the old, traditional method where we
keep it in fixed deposits and our
returns come from that, we manage our expenses from that.
Subscribing directly depends
on that scenario. It can be quite risky, so this is a
very good solution for us,
even for those who have
not planned for themselves,
because it can start with immediate attention,
and also for those who can
wait for some time. Subscribe for your pension. Your
investment in this should be this much. There is no
maximum investment limit in a year.
You can subscribe by payment. I am
entering the entries on different screens.
You can check them and
take a screenshot of it. There is a
dedicated option to check it easily.  You can avail this in two ways.
You can avail this option. You can avail this option in the form of
duty option which means you will start
getting pension from now onwards. This option will
suit those people. The second option
is duty option which means you can select
any period between one year to 10 years
and after that you will get the pension start
here. There are
many options available for availing this pension.
Now we are talking about the option which
came for the first time in the market and the best option is Amazon
Live with Written Purchases which means that
whatever investment you have made, you will get
annual
returns and your pension will continue for your entire life. For
example, if you invested Rs. 2000000,
then you will keep getting
more than Rs. 90 lakh and you will get the
money you invested
and
even after taking Rs. 1 lakh, you will continue to get it. The second
option is to turn off that flashlight which
means that whatever you had tweeted that you had
subscribed to the war and whatever pension you will get will be that.
1728 which you will keep
getting till this time and
in the event of your death, your balance of ₹1000000 will be
given to Navami, which is a very
good feature. The third option is of
Intensity of Life with written of medium
from 2006, which means that if you are
76 years old, you had invested even 5% of your
money, for example, if you
subscribe and your balance will be 1 lakh 4751,
which will happen if you die, then the
balance will be there. Now let's talk about the
best option in debt, that is, you can turn on
your Reduce Food and Beauty of
Life where to purchase and
in the Permanent Disability option, the company
gives flexibility that if there is any
critical disease or permanent
disability due to an accident, then the
company will return the entire investment amount to you
and your option will
continue, if you invest in it
and wait for 10 years, then you will not be tensed.  It will be
16,700 rupees, which the youth
can check. Apart from this, the option which is there is
the return of premium single
point,
which means that your premium will
not be returned, but if something happens to you tomorrow, then
after you get your pension, your wife will continue to subscribe and
she will continue to get pension. The second option is A
Beautiful Live Subscribe, which is the same, in the
event of your death, your wife will continue to
get pension. In this, you can select the return premium
option, company subscribe option for yourself,
whichever you feel, if
you subscribe, you can select duty
so that you can take advantage of the market's maximum
rate of interest which is 11.51.
We are
putting the list of rate of interest on the screen, which you
can also check, you can
take a screenshot of it and check it for the future.
If you invest in this scheme for 2 years, then the
company gives you an
extra rate of interest.
If you feel
that our option is less, then you
can top up it.  It
is available in both minute and department options. There is
no limit of any kind in this. For
example, if you invest Rs 20 lakh in duty
and wait for 10 years, then
your annual benefit will
be Rs 26,961 and if you top up Rs 10 lakh for 5 years,
which will be
added to your 8104 savings after 8.1 years, and
after that your annual benefit will be
Rs 360,003, which can be a very good option. The
company sees that you
can subscribe to their booster
for existing customers, which means
that if you are an existing customer,
then you will get the company's benefit extra in the plan. For example,
if you are a new customer
and you invest Rs 1,18,670, then the benefit
of existing customers will be Rs 19,800,57,
which is a
new feature for existing customers. This is their third
generation plan.  That if you
take this then it can be run for 3 generations
if the father cases the appointed president,
his son will get pension and if the
video is soon then he too will get the
entire
investment amount back to your family member. Subscribe
If the policy holder of that department plan
dies then whatever is your
investment, 15 percent or the
purchase price
quid guaranteed bonus is more than the loss,
it will be given to the nominee.
You have to select the time of department
before taking the policy, you
cannot change it later, if you
transfer from this scheme to the appointment
thumb and invest your money in it, then
you will get the benefit of additional pension
in this, you also have to keep in mind that
whatever your tension is, it will be made according to the
loss, so this can take away our and our
subscribers, but
select your product as per your own choice, like it,
if you liked the video then
share it with those people who are
applying for jobs, if we keep bringing such videos,
please subscribe to our channel  Like and
subscribe, thank you for
watching